therawfoodworld.com 2010-01-19

# The Raw Food World - Vibrant Health through A Raw Food Lifestyle :

**Privacy Policy Statment**   
Raw Vegan Books Inc. will **NEVER** sell or exchange your personal information (name, email address and mailing address) to anyone. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for all URL's contained within the Raw Vegan Books web site. Please be aware that some of the URL's contained on our web site link to OUTSIDE of this site. Please be advised that those sites do not follow our policy statement. Information collected at our web site, will be used for INTERNAL use only. Your information will never be revealed to an outside 3rd party. Any information you share with us is held with the utmost care and security, and will not be used in ways in which you have not agreed. Any material we send to our customers via e-mail or postal mail, we always have an OPT OUT option for visitors that choose not to receive future mailings. Raw Vegan Books respects the privacy of all users who visit this site. No effort is made to identify individuals without their prior knowledge and approval. The following policies are in effect for all of the web pages owned and operated by Raw Vegan Books: 

**PERSONAL INFORMATION:** On all of our input forms we ask users to provide their e-mail address and/or mailing address for the intended purpose of the form. This site maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. Your e-mail address or street address will not be sold to a third party and is only used for the stated purpose of the form. Whenever the identity of a visitor is requested, we clearly indicate the purpose of the request. You may easily be removed from the list at any time by going to http://www.LivingNutritionals.com or calling 800-642-4113. 

**LOG FILES:** When a visitor views any of our pages, like all web servers, our system logs the visitor's domain name and/or IP address. We collect the domain names and/or IP addresses in order to compile information on what pages visitors successfully access, and what pages they may have experienced any technical difficulties with. This allows us to make improvements and upgrades to the site as needed. This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and is completely anonymous. The information is never used to identify any individuals. 

**BROWSER COOKIES:** Our on-line store uses "cookies" to store specific information about a customers account (if cookies are enabled in the customer's browser). This cookie is a small file containing encrypted data pertinent to the customer's account, such as their name. The cookie is stored on the customer's computer and cannot be viewed by other sites. The information contained in it is only used for storing account information for future visits. 

**CUSTOMER RECORDS:** When customers make a purchase from our on-line store, customer records are never sold to a third party. 

**SECURE TRANSACTIONS:** When a visitor provides certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to our payment gateway's secure server. We use authorize.net for payment processing. For more information please read their privacy policy located at: http://www.authorize.net/company/privacy.php 

Raw Vegan Books reserves the right to change its on-line policy at any time. Future changes will be duly noted on this page. If you have any other questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at any time Contact Raw Vegan Books. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy you may reach us on our contact us page. 

**Contact Living Nutritinals:**   
If you have any questions regaurding our privacy policy you may reach us on our [contact us page](http://www.therawfoodworld.com/contactus.html). 

This page was last update on September 12, 2004
